(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
まもなく開始！
Starting soon!
夢見た世界が
The world I dreamed of
目の前で動き出す
Starts moving before my eyes
まだ見ぬ明日へ
Toward the tomorrow yet unseen
手を伸ばして
Reach out your hand
アクリルパネル
出演タレントの箔押し複製サイン入り！
Acrylic Panel
Includes foil-stamped replica signatures of the performing talent!
心の奥に
Deep in my heart
秘めた想い解き放って
Releasing the hidden feelings
新しい世界へ
Toward a new world
飛び出そう
Let's leap out
輝く未来を
The shining future
信じているから
Because I believe in it
ホロウィッチ公式X発！人気マンガ
ウルトラジャンプ出張連載中！！
From holoWitches Official X! Popular Manga
Serializing in Ultra Jump!!
どんな困難も
No matter what difficulties
乗り越えていける
I can overcome them
仲間と共に
Together with my friends
歩んでいこう
Let's walk forward
奇跡を信じて
Believe in miracles
魔法をかけて
Cast a spell
夢は終わらない
The dream doesn't end
続いていくから
Because it will continue
最高の笑顔で
With the best smile
歌い続けよう
Let's keep singing
君に届け
Reach to you
このメロディ
This melody
永遠の絆
Eternal bond
結んでいこう
Let's tie it
アクリルパネル
出演タレントの箔押し複製サイン入り！
Acrylic Panel
Includes foil-stamped replica signatures of the performing talent!
夢見た世界が
The world I dreamed of
目の前で動き出す
Starts moving before my eyes
まだ見ぬ明日へ
Toward the tomorrow yet unseen
手を伸ばして
Reach out your hand
心の奥に
Deep in my heart
秘めた想い解き放って
Releasing the hidden feelings
新しい世界へ
Toward a new world
飛び出そう
Let's leap out
ホロウィッチ公式X発！人気マンガ
ウルトラジャンプ出張連載中！！
From holoWitches Official X! Popular Manga
Serializing in Ultra Jump!!
輝く未来を
The shining future
信じているから
Because I believe in it
どんな困難も
No matter what difficulties
乗り越えていける
I can overcome them
仲間と共に
Together with my friends
歩んでいこう
Let's walk forward
奇跡を信じて
Believe in miracles
魔法をかけて
Cast a spell
アクリルパネル
出演タレントの箔押し複製サイン入り！
Acrylic Panel
Includes foil-stamped replica signatures of the performing talent!
夢は終わらない
The dream doesn't end
続いていくから
Because it will continue
最高の笑顔で
With the best smile
歌い続けよう
Let's keep singing
君に届け
Reach to you
このメロディ
This melody
永遠の絆
Eternal bond
結んでいこう
Let's tie it
まもなく開始
Starting Soon
僕たち6人は、配信アプリ「ホロキャス」で活動する配信者。
We six are streamers active on the streaming app "HoloCas."
突然画面に吸い込まれて、アプリと繋がる謎の世界、ホロキャス界に来ちゃった！
Suddenly, we were sucked into the screen and ended up in "HoloCas World," a mysterious world connected to the app!
そこでは、現実で苦しむ人の魂が怪物化してしまう現象、「夢落ち」が起こっていた。
There, a phenomenon called "Dream-fall" was occurring, where the souls of people suffering in reality turned into monsters.
怪物コドプサーを倒して、みんなの魂を取り戻さないと！
We have to defeat the monster Codopsa and take back everyone's souls!
そうして私たちは、魔法少女に変身して戦うことになった。
And so, we transformed into magical girls and decided to fight.
みんなの心を助けて、夢を応援する！
Helping everyone's hearts and supporting their dreams!
それが、魔法少女ホロウィッチ！
That is, Magical Girl holoWitches!
私、大きくなったら魔法少女になりたい。
I want to be a magical girl when I grow up.
魔法で、いろんな人を助けるの。
I'll help all sorts of people with magic.
面倒な仕事、みんな私に押し付けて、丸投げして。
Everyone pushes their troublesome work onto me, just dumping it all.
やったやったらで好き勝手言って、何なのよ。
And when I do it, they just say whatever they want. What's the deal?
何なのよ。
What is this...?
みなさん、こんにちは！
Everyone, hello!
会場にお越しいただき、ありがとうございます。
Thank you for coming to the venue today.
さて、本日はこれからスペシャルなショーを...
Now, today we'll be presenting a special show...
ちょっと待ってもらおうか！！
Hold on just a minute!!
ほほう、ずいぶん人が集まってるじゃねえか。
Ho-ho, looks like quite a crowd has gathered.
あ、あなたたち、何者ですか！？
Wh-who are you?!
お前ら人間どもを恐怖と絶望のどん底に叩き落として、
We'll knock you humans down into the depths of fear and despair,
夢落ちさせる。
and make you fall into a nightmare.
それが俺たち、コドプサー！
That's us, the Codopsa!
大変！こんな時は、あの子たちを呼ぶしかない！
Oh no! At a time like this, we have no choice but to call those girls!
皆さんも声を揃えて呼んでくださいね。
Everyone, please join your voices and call for them.
せーの！
Ready, set...
助けて、ホロウィッチ！
Help us, holoWitches!
な、なんだ！？
Wh-what?!
ホロウィッチボトル！
HoloWitch Bottle!
インキュート！
Incute!
この手を差し伸べ、掴んで、握る。
Reaching out this hand, grabbing, and holding on.
天使のホロ。魔法少女かなた！
Angel holo. Magical Girl Kanata!
みんなの願いを咲かせる祈り。巫女のホロ。
A prayer that makes everyone's wishes bloom. Shrine maiden holo.
魔法少女みこ！
Magical Girl Miko!
甘い幸せ、お裾分け。姫のホロ。
Sharing a little sweet happiness. Princess holo.
魔法少女ルーナ！
Magical Girl Luna!
煌めくお宝、ロックオン！海賊のホロ。
Locking onto glittering treasures! Pirate holo.
魔法少女マリン！
Magical Girl Marine!
眠れる深淵、わがままに。魔女のホロ。
Selfishly, in the sleeping abyss. Witch holo.
魔法少女シオン！
Magical Girl Shion!
荒波を往く不敵な牙。シャチのホロ。
Fearless fangs navigating through rough waves. Orca holo.
魔法少女クロエ！
Magical Girl Chloe!
ホロウィッチ、コンジャンクション！
holoWitches, Conjunction!
はじまりの魔法 -charm-
Hashimari no Mahou -charm-
君に魔法をかけるよ
I'll cast a spell on you
We can share our dreams
始まりを告げる ショータイムが響く
The showtime that heralds the beginning resonates
気づいた時がいつだってスタートラインなんだ
The moment you realize it is always the start line
何者でもなかった日々を越え
Beyond the days when I was nobody
歌おう
Let's sing
見つけたあなたの中に ちっぽけな
I found it inside of you, a tiny
輝きの原石
gemstone of brilliance.
どうして私だけ上手くいかないんだろう
Why am I the only one who can't do things right?
自分以外の全てが眩しく見えるけど
Everything except me looks so dazzling.
ねえ君に見つけて欲しくて
Hey, I want you to find me.
なりたい私になる今こそ
Now is the time to become the me I want to be.
そうだ叶えたい 掴みたい 夢があるから
That's right, because I have dreams I want to fulfill and grasp.
塞ぎ込んだ日々の事も連れ出すんだ
I'll take even those gloomy days with me.
信じる力が奇跡起こすように
So that the power of belief can make a miracle happen.
君に魔法をかけるよ We cast a spell on your dream
I'll cast a spell on you, we cast a spell on your dream.
叶わぬ望みと 叶わない願い
Unattainable wishes and unfulfillable desires,
それぞれが等しく流れてく世界で
in a world where each flows equally.
何を求めて歩き続けるんだろう
I wonder what I'm walking towards, searching for.
いつもそんな事ばかり迷うけど
I'm always lost in thoughts like that,
君がくれたこの空が
but this sky that you gave me
消えない翼をくれたね
gave me wings that won't disappear.
そうだ照らしたい 届けたい 人がいるから
That's right, because there's someone I want to shine for and reach.
誰一人置いて行ったりしないと決めたんだ
I've decided I won't leave anyone behind.
愛したい 答えたい 自分自身の
I want to love, I want to answer my own
正解なんて越えて行こう 未体験のステージ
correct answer, let's go beyond to an unexperienced stage.
どんな場所でもいいよ
Any place is fine.
どんな姿でもいい
Any appearance is fine.
追いかけたいんだ あの煌めきを
I want to chase after that sparkle.
希望 今は光 痛み 全て
Hope, now light, pain, everything...
抱きしめて持って行こう
let's embrace it all and take it with us.
ほら繋げたい 広げたい 道があるから
Look, because there's a path I want to connect and expand.
ここから始まる物語を一緒に行こう
Let's go together into the story that starts here.
信じる力が奇跡起こすように
So that the power of belief can make a miracle happen.
この手を握って 一人じゃないから
Take this hand, because you're not alone.
君に魔法をかけるよ We cast a spell on your dream
I'll cast a spell on you, we cast a spell on your dream.
ホラップサー、撃退完了ー！
Holapser, repelled!
ありがとう、ホロウィッチ！ すっごくかっこよかったよ！
Thank you, HoloWitch! You were so cool!
ホラップサーは、あれで全部かな？
Was that all of the Holapsers?
そうじゃない？ でかいのが出てきそうな感じもしないし。
I think so? It doesn't feel like a big one is coming out either.
じゃあ、もう戦い終わりなのかな？
So, is the battle over now?
今回はサクッと勝てて良かったななね！
It's great we won so easily this time, nanane!
いつも結構苦戦させられるもんね。
We usually struggle quite a bit.
船長たちも魔法少女が板についてきたってことかな？
Does that mean we've finally settled into our roles as magical girls?
そうですね、もう何度も魔法を使って戦ってましたし。
That's right, we've fought using magic so many times already.
魔法！ ファンの皆さんももっとホロウィッチの魔法が見たいと思いますよ！
Magic! I'm sure the fans want to see more of HoloWitch's magic too!
んじゃ、エリートの魔法いっちゃお！
Well then, let's show off some elite magic!
いっちゃおうかな？
Should we?
6人でっていうのはさっきやったし、今度は3人ずつチームに分かれてみる？
We just did it with all six of us, so how about we split into teams of three this time?
賛成ななな！ まずはルーナたちがやるななな！
I agree, nanana! Luna's team will go first, nanana!
じゃ、お手並み拝見といきましょう。
Then, let's see what you can do.
がんばってねー！
Good luck!
がんばれー！
Do your best!
がんばってー！
You can do it!
よし、じゃあ行くならよ！
Alright, let's go!
せーの！
Ready, set...
ホロウィッチ、チーム・ラスタ、フルキャスト！
HoloWitch, Team Lasta, full cast!
甘くて幸せなこと
Sweet and happy things,
隠し味は何にしよう
what should I use for the secret ingredient?
純粋な乙女心
Pure maidenly heart,
甘い恋も絡めなくちゃ
I have to mix in sweet love too.
切なさもちょっと混ぜてみる Feel you
Try mixing in a bit of sadness, Feel you.
酸味も積み上げたらタルト
If you stack up the sourness too, it's a tart.
苦味も...
Even the bitterness...
チョコレートケーキ...
Is like a chocolate cake...
魔法をかけた
Casting magic on it...
甘い奇跡
To create a sweet miracle!
甘さは抑えてみたのとか
Maybe I tried to hold back on the sweetness?
ミルクなしのコーヒーとか
Like coffee without any milk?
甘いだけじゃ大人になれないの？
Can't I become an adult just by being sweet?
そんなの絶対絶対ヤダヤダヤダ
I absolutely, absolutely don't want that!
ねえ あげようか
Hey, shall I give it to you?
甘い罠
This sweet trap.
ほら 虜にしてあげる
Look, I'll make you fall for me.
そんな魔法かけるから
Since I'm casting that kind of magic...
ちょっとだけ待たせてあげるわ
I'll make you wait just a little bit.
尊と一口が足りなくて
Just a single bite wasn't enough.
赤いちごみたく意地張って
Being stubborn like a red strawberry...
甘いところなんて見せないわ
I won't show you my sweet side.
完璧に作る魔法 独り占めで もうもうもう
Keeping this perfect magic all to myself, oh!
ねえ 気づいてるでしょ？
Hey, you've noticed, haven't you?
分かってるでしょ？
You know it, don't you?
隠し味の恋心
The secret ingredient is my love.
苦味とか
Whether it's bitterness...
酸味とか
Or whether it's sourness...
そういうのもたまにはいいわ
Those are fine once in a while.
意地っ張りで
Stubborn...
我儘な
And selfish...
そんな甘い魔法使い
That's the kind of sweet magic user I am.
チームラスタ、素敵な魔法をありがとう！
Team Lasta, thank you for the wonderful magic!
めっちゃ良かったじゃん。こっちも頑張らないとな。
That was really good. We have to do our best too.
せっかくだし、次はちょっと雰囲気変えてみない？
Since we're here, why don't we change the mood a bit?
いいですね！じゃあ...
Sounds good! Well then...
せーの！ホロウィッチ！チームアストラ！フルキャスト！
Ready, go! Holowitch! Team Astra! Full Cast!
空にある何かを見つめてたら
As I gazed at something in the sky...
それは星だって君が教えてくれた
You told me that it was a star.
まるでそれは僕らみたいに寄り添ってる
It's as if it's snuggling up, just like us.
それを泣いたり笑ったり繋いでゆく
Connecting those moments of laughter and tears.
何十回 何百回 ぶつかりあって
Colliding tens, hundreds of times...
何十年 何百年 昔の光が
Light from tens, hundreds of years ago...
星自身も忘れた頃に僕らに届いてる
Reaches us even after the star itself has forgotten.
僕ら付き合って 手繰りあって 同じ空
We're together, pulling each other along under the same sky.
輝くのだって 二人だって 約束した
We promised each other that we'd shine together.
遥か遠く終わらないベテルギウス
A distant, never-ending Betelgeuse.
誰かに繋ぐ魔法
Magic that connects to someone.
僕ら肩並べて 取り合って 進んでく
Standing side-by-side, holding hands, we move forward.
辛い時だって 泣かないって 誓ったはず
We should have sworn not to cry, even in hard times.
遥か遠く終わらないベテルギウス
A distant, never-ending Betelgeuse.
君にも見えるだろう
You can see it too, right?
祈りが
Our prayer.
記憶を辿るたび 蘇るよ
It all comes back whenever I trace my memories.
君がいつだって そこにいてくれること
The fact that you're always there for me.
まるでそれは星の光
It's just like the light of a star.
...と同じように
...just like...
今日泣いたり笑ったり繋いでいく
Connecting through today's tears and laughter
何十回 何百回 ぶつかり合って
Clashing dozens, hundreds of times
何十年 何百年前の光が
The light from decades, centuries ago
僕自身も忘れたころに
Just when I'd forgotten myself
僕らを照らしてる
Is shining upon us
僕ら見つけ合って 辿り合って 同じ空
We found each other, reached each other, under the same sky
輝くのだって 二人だって 約束した
We promised to shine, the two of us
遥か遠く終わらないベテルギウス
Betelgeuse, far away and unending
誰かに繋ぐ魔法
A magic to connect to someone
どこまで いつまで 生きられるか
How far, for how long can we live?
君が不安になるたびに強がるんだ
I act tough whenever you get anxious
大丈夫 僕が横にいるよ
It's okay, I'm right beside you
見えない線を繋ごう
Let's connect the invisible lines
僕ら見つけ合って 辿り合って 同じ空
We found each other, reached each other, under the same sky
輝くのだって 二人だって 約束した
We promised to shine, the two of us
遥か遠く終わらないベテルギウス
Betelgeuse, far away and unending
誰かに繋ぐ魔法
A magic to connect to someone
僕ら肩並べて 取り合って 進んでいく
We walk side-by-side, holding hands, moving forward
辛い時だって 二人だって 誓っただろ
We swore we'd be together even in hard times, right?
遥か遠く終わらないベテルギウス
Betelgeuse, far away and unending
君にも見えるだろう 祈りが
You can see it too, can't you? This prayer...
空にある何かを見つめてたら
As we gazed at something in the sky
それは星だって君が教えてくれた
You told me that it was a star
チーム・アストラノ魔法も、すごくいい雰囲気でしたね。
Team Astra's magic had a great atmosphere too, didn't it?
これ、思ったよりきつい…
This is tougher than I thought...
ちょ、ちょ、みんな大丈夫？
Wait, wait, is everyone okay?
アエル、なんか魔法使いすぎてる。これじゃみんなの力がもたないよ。
Aru, they're using too much magic. Everyone's strength won't hold out like this.
大丈夫、まだやれるから。
It's okay, we can still go on.
はい。この人を助けるためには…
Yes. To save this person...
でも…
But...
もっと見せてください、ホロウィッチ。
Please show me more, Holowitches.
え？もしかしてMCのお姉さん？
Eh? Is that the MC lady?
魔法…魔法を。
Magic... give me magic.
魔法、魔法、魔法、魔法。魔法見せて。ね、魔法を。魔法少女の魔法を見せて！
Magic, magic, magic, magic. Show me magic. Hey, magic. Show me the magical girls' magic!
あ、ちょ、お姉さん？
Ah, wait, lady?
いけない、ホロウィッチ。これ以上は…
Stop, Holowitches. Any more than this...
いけない？
Stop?
だめなの？どうしてだめなの？
Is it bad? Why is it bad?
魔法少女でしょ。
You're magical girls, aren't you?
見せて！勝って！魔法！魔法！魔法！！
Show me! Win! Magic! Magic! Magic!!
この感じ、なんか来るよ。やばいのが。
This feeling, something's coming. Something bad.
いいな、魔法。魔法少女。
Magic is nice. Magical girls.
私もなりたかった。ずっと、ずっと、ずっと、ずっと、ずっと、ずっと。
I wanted to be one too. Forever, forever, forever, forever, forever, forever.
あなたたちみたいな魔法少女になりたかった。
I wanted to be a magical girl like you all.
なりたかったのに！！
I wanted to be one, and yet!!
お姉さん！？
Lady!?
私も…
I also...
あんな風になりたかった。
I wanted to be like that.
かっこよく魔法を使って。
Using magic coolly.
誰かを助けて。
Helping someone.
毎日充実して。
Living a fulfilling life every day.
あんな風に輝いて笑える自分になりたかった。
I wanted to be someone who could shine and smile like that.
なのに違う！
But it's different!
今の私は、惨めで、不様で。
Current me is miserable and pathetic.
何も、何も、何も、何も、何もない！
Nothing, nothing, nothing, nothing, I have nothing!
あんなに好きだった魔法少女も
The magical girl I loved so much,
見れば見るほど虚しくなって
the more I look at her, the emptier I feel.
あんなふうになれなかったんだなーって
Thinking, "I couldn't become like that..."
どうしてもそう思っちゃって
I just can't help but think that.
やだ...
No...
やだよ...
I don't want to...
好きなものくらい...
At least my favorite things...
ずっと好きでいたいのに！
...I want to keep loving them forever!
愛して愛して愛して
作詞・作曲: きくお
Love Me, Love Me, Love Me
Lyrics & Composition: Kikuo
遥か遠い遠い昔　巻かれた首輪
Far, far away, long ago, a collar was wrapped.
人が欲しい　人が欲しいと叫ぶ　呪いの首輪
"I want people, I want people," screamed the cursed collar.
怒らないで　見捨てないで　どこも行かないで
Don't be angry, don't abandon me, don't go anywhere.
強く締める　吐くまで締める　人がいない　いないと
Tighten it hard, tighten it until I vomit, there's no one, no one here.
いい成績でしょう　ねえ　ねえ　いい子でしょう
I have good grades, right? Hey, hey, I'm a good girl, right?
かわいい子でしょう　ねえ　ねえ　いい子でしょう
I'm a cute girl, right? Hey, hey, I'm a good girl, right?
苦しいんで
It's painful.
愛して　愛して　愛して
Love me, love me, love me.
もっともっと　愛して
Love me more and more.
愛して　愛して
Love me, love me.
狂おしいほどに
To the point of going crazy.
苦しい　苦しい
It's painful, it's painful.
呪縛を　解いて解いて　ねえ
Break the spell, break it, please.
止められない　嗚呼
It can't be stopped, ah.
嗚呼
Ah...
身体　身体　大きくなっても小さい首輪
Even as my body, my body grows, the collar remains small.
苦しくなる　足りなくなる　人が　人が　足りない
It gets painful, it's not enough, people, people aren't enough.
クラスの誰にも負けない　綺麗な子でしょう
I'm a prettier girl than anyone in the class, right?
あの娘よりも　どの娘よりも　誰も彼も　私を見てよ
Better than that girl, better than any girl, everyone, look at me!
体育館裏　あなたに告白を
Behind the gym, I'll confess to you.
嘘みたいでしょう　あなたが好きなの　汚いあなたが
It's like a lie, right? I like you, the filthy you.
愛して　愛して　愛して
Love me, love me, love me.
全部あげる　あなたに　あなたに
I'll give you everything, to you, to you.
全部背負ってもらうよ
I'll have you carry everything.
足りない　あなたが足りない
It's not enough, you're not enough.
離さないよ　嗚呼
I won't let you go, ah.
ごめんなさい
I'm sorry.
愛して　愛して　愛して
Love me, love me, love me.
もっともっと　愛して
Love me more and more.
愛して　愛して
Love me, love me.
狂おしいほどに
To the point of going crazy.
苦しい　離さない
It's painful, I won't let go.
苦しい　もっともっと　ねえ
It's painful, more and more, please.
幸せなの　嗚呼
I'm happy, ah.
嗚呼ー！
Aah--!
お姉さんが...
Big sis...
コラプサーに取り込まれてるっ！
She's being absorbed by a Corruptor!
悲しい気持ちが大きくなりすぎて、コラプサーの力が増しちゃったんだ。
Her sadness grew too great, and it's boosted the Corrupter's power.
えーっ！？なんでなんでなんでー！？
Ehh!? Why, why, why!?
このショーってあれですよね。お姉さんが魔法少女好きすぎて、それでこういうの作っちゃったーってやつですよね？
This show is that thing, right? The sister loved magical girls so much that she created all of this.
そう。だからみこたちが魔法使ってるとこたくさん見せられたら、
Right. So she thought if she could see Miko and the others using magic,
不安とか悲しいとかそういうのなくせるかもーって。
it might take away her anxiety and sadness.
あぁ…
Ah...
逆か…
It's the opposite...
逆？
Opposite?
いや、あのお姉さんさ、マジで魔法少女が好きで、魔法少女になりたくて。
No, you see, she really loved magical girls and wanted to be one.
でもなれなくて諦めたわけじゃん。
But she couldn't, so she had to give up on it.
そっか…
I see...
好きだけど、本当にめちゃくちゃ好きだけど、でもだからこそ実際に目にすると、
She loves them, she really does, but that's why when she actually sees them,
自分はそうはなれなかったんだって思って、好きなはずなのに苦しいって感じちゃうんだ。
she's reminded she couldn't become one. It feels painful even though she loves it.
あの人自身、気づいてなかったのかも。
She might not have realized it herself.
大好きな魔法少女のショーを見られたら、また元気を取り戻せるかもって。
She thought seeing her favorite magical girl show would cheer her up.
あのコラプサー、こうなるってわかってて、
That Corrupter knew this would happen,
それで敢えてお姉さんにショーをさせてたのか！
and that's why it dared to make her perform the show!
なんで…なんでこうなっちゃったの？
Why... why did it turn out like this?
なんで苦しいの止まらないの？
Why won't this pain stop?
何をしてても、何を考えてても…
No matter what I do, no matter what I think...
なんで…なんで楽しいより、苦しいの方が大きくなっちゃうの…？
Why... why does the pain feel bigger than the joy...?
きゃあああ！
Kyaaaa!
ホロウィッチー！
HoloWitch!
ううっ…あれ？あれって…
Ugh... Wait? What's that...?
頑張るにぇー！諦めない心にぇ！！
Do your best! A heart that doesn't give up!!
コメント…
Comments...
これ、今ここがホロキャストと繋がってる？
Is this place connected to Holocast right now?
リアルタイムで配信されてるんだ！
It's being streamed in real-time!
じゃあ、このコメント、リスナーのみんなの…
Then these comments are from all the listeners...
みんなが…見てる人、一人ひとりが…
Everyone... every single person watching...
みこたちのこと、応援してくれてる。
they're all cheering for us.
頑張れって言ってくれてる。
They're telling us to do our best.
ルーナたちだけじゃないのら。
It's not just for us, nora.
お姉さんのことも、頑張ってほしい、幸せになってほしいって思ってくれてる。
They want her to do her best and be happy too.
背中も、心も、心から、押してくれてる！
They're supporting us, pushing our hearts from the bottom of theirs!
みんなの気持ちで、みんなの心が…
With everyone's feelings, everyone's hearts...
光が輝く！
The light shines bright!
チェンジ！
Change!
ガーディアンアームズ！！
Guardian Arms!!
これだけ背中を押されたら、飛び込んでいくしかない！
With this much support, I have no choice but to dive in!
ねぇな！！
Right!?
ふんっ！
Hmph!
てりゃ！
Terya!
おりゃ！
Orya!
そーりゃ！
Sorya!
うわあぁぁぁ！
Uwaaaaa!
なんかこっち敵多いんだけど！
Why are there so many enemies over here!?
チェンジ！
Change!
みこみこナイト！！
Mikomiko Knight!!
セイクレッドシュフェアー！！
Sacred Sphere!!
ええいっ！
Eei!
せいっ！
Sei!
おらぁ！
Oraa!
そーり、そーれ！それ！それぇ！
So-ri, so-re! There! Take that!
はっ！
Ha!
魔法少女にぴったりの可愛いルナたん！
The adorable Luna-tan is perfect as a magical girl!
んな姫、ただ守られるだけの助手ではない。
Princess, you're not an assistant who just needs protecting.
姫様のご活躍お祈り申し上げます！！！！！
I pray for your success, Princess!!!!!
ルーナもやるのら！
Luna is going to do it, too!
チェンジ・キャンディ！
Change Candy!
甘いのら。
Too naive.
ありがとう、一味の君たち。
Thank you, my Crew.
本当、いいお宝ね！
Truly, a fine treasure!
チェンジ・ガンマリナ！
Change Gun-Marina!
チェンジ・ブルーミング・ルーム！
Change Blooming Room!
シオンちゃんのおかげで
人生今めっちゃ楽しい！！
Thanks to Shion-chan,
life is so much fun right now!!
オッケー、ありがとう。
Okay, thank you.
バイオレット・レイ！
Violet Ray!
チェンジ・オルカ・スナッパー！
Change Orca Snapper!
よし、なりきっていきましょー！
Alright, let's get into character!
あなたは、どうして魔法少女に
なりたかったの？
Why did you want to become
a magical girl?
どうしてって...
Why?
色んな魔法が使えて、素敵で、カッコよくて...
Because you can use all kinds of magic,
it's wonderful, it's cool...
うんうん、そっね。
Yeah, that's right.
魔法少女になってさ、どんなことがしたかった？
Having become a magical girl,
what did you want to do?
お姉さんの好きな魔法少女は、
どんなことをしてたのら？
What kind of things did
the magical girl you liked do?
人を助けてた。
She was helping people.
魔法で素敵にカッコよく。
With magic, wonderfully and coolly.
そう、そこが魔法少女のいいところよね。
Right, that's the great thing
about being a magical girl.
そこが好きだったんなら、あなたは
魔法少女になりたかったっていうより...
If that's what you liked, then maybe
instead of wanting to be a magical girl...
誰かの力になれる誰かに、
なりたかったんじゃない？
You wanted to be someone
who could help others?
誰かの力になれる、誰か...
Someone who could help others...
どんな小さなことでも、ちょっとしたことでも、
No matter how small or simple it is,
誰かの力になれるなら、それって
魔法少女と一緒じゃん。
if you're helping someone,
that's just like being a magical girl.
お姉さんが好きだった魔法少女は、
きっとそれを教えてくれてたのら。
The magical girl you liked must have
been teaching you that.
そうそう。
Exactly.
だからさ、魔法が使えるかどうかは
関係ないんじゃない？
So, whether you can use magic or not
doesn't really matter, does it?
あなたが好きだった魔法少女が教えてくれた、
The lesson you learned from
the magical girl you liked...
誰かの力になれるのが素敵でカッコいいって
いう気持ち。
...that the desire to help someone
is wonderful and cool.
それがあなたのホロ。
That's your 'Holo.'
あなたの一番のお宝。
Your most precious treasure.
私... 私の...
Me... mine...
コロプサーの力が弱まってる！
Colopsor's power is weakening!
今だ、ホロウィッチ！
Now's the time, HoloWitch!
チェンジ・ホロウィッチ・シンフォニー！
Change HoloWitch Symphony!
フルキャスト！
Full Cast!
大丈夫ですか？
Are you okay?
うん。
Yeah.
ありがとう。
Thank you.
それと... ごめんなさい。
And... I'm sorry.
あなたたちを巻き込んでしまって...
I ended up getting you all involved...
いいのいいの、気にしないで。
It's okay, it's okay, don't worry about it.
船長たちがホロウィッチになったのは、
The reason we became HoloWitches
夢落ちした人を助けるためなんだから。
was to save people who fell into despair.
そっか。
I see.
あなたたちみんな、本当に魔法少女なんだね。
You guys are all truly magical girls, aren't you?
魔法が使えるからじゃなくて...
Not because you can use magic...
...誰かの力になれたらって思う、その心が。
...but because of your hearts, wanting to help.
私もなれるかな...
I wonder if I can become one too...
誰かの力になれる誰かに。
Someone who can be a help to others.
うーん、みんなはどう思う？
Hmm, what do you all think?
応援してます / 出来る！ 絶対に出来る！ / 頑張って
Supporting you / You can do it! / Good luck
だって！お姉さんならきっと大丈夫なな。
See? If it's you, I'm sure you'll be fine.
うん、頑張ってみる。
Yeah, I'll try my best.
ありがとう、ホロウィッチ！
Thank you, HoloWitch!
あの人の心、現実の世界に帰れたんだ。
That person's heart was able to return to the real world.
もう安心だよ、ホロウィッチ。
Everything's okay now, HoloWitch.
そっか... よかったぁ。
I see... Thank goodness.
これでめでたしめでたし。
And with that, they lived happily ever after.
でもいいんだけど、せっかくホロキャスト繋がってて
But since we're connected to HoloCast
リスナーの皆さんが見てくれてるんだし、ここはやっぱり...
and the listeners are watching, shouldn't we...
歌う？
Sing?
歌っちゃう？
Should we sing?
歌っちゃうのなー！
Let's sing-nanora!
アイル、ラグ、戻るのちょっと後になってもいい？
Aile, Lagu, is it okay if we head back a little later?
もちろん！
Of course!
じゃあ僕らは先に戻って準備してるから。
Then we'll head back first and get things ready.
好きなだけ楽しんでから戻ってきてね。
Come back after you've enjoyed yourselves.
いつもの一日から抜け出して
Breaking out of the usual day
目が覚めるような冒険の旅
An eye-opening adventurous journey
回る地球儀を目印に
With the spinning globe as our landmark
さあ会いに行こう 特別な一日に
Now let's go meet a special day
見鳥もゆる 新しい季節に
In the new season where greenery buds
一人見つめた ブルーライト
Staring alone at the blue light
顔も知らない 友達に送る
Sending to a friend whose face I don't know
招待状のメッセージ
A message of invitation
孤独じゃない もう正反対に
Not lonely, just the opposite now
ドクドク動き出す 毎日
Days that start beating "thump-thump"
でもやっと会えたね 想像と現実が
But we finally met, imagination and reality
交わって高鳴る胸 抑えられない
Crossing over, I can't suppress my heart
約束の場所は
The promised place is
夢見ていた場所
The place I was dreaming of
忘れられない 一日が今始まる
An unforgettable day is beginning now
待ちに待った今日は 特別な日
Today is the special day I've been waiting for
日常から 少しはみ出して
Stepping out of the everyday life a little
ほらシャッターを切って 写し出せば
Look, if you press the shutter and capture it
あふれだす 零れる笑顔ばかり
It's full of nothing but overflowing smiles
煌めき出した 飛び乗ったコースターも
The roller coaster I jumped on started to sparkle
朝までだって 夢中だよ
I'll be obsessed with it until morning
かけがえのない 瞬間が溢れてる
Precious moments are overflowing
待ち時間さえも 愛しく思える
Even the waiting time feels precious
次はどこに行こうか
Where should we go next?
軽やかに歩く
Walking lightly
不思議なほどに 気がつけば好きでいる時間
It's strange how much I realize I love this time
太陽が沈んだ 街を飾る
Decorating the town where the sun has set
光が織りなす パレードに
In the parade woven by lights
心奪われ 噛み締める
My heart is stolen, and I cherish it
ああ本当に ここに来てよかったな
Ah, I'm really glad I came here
待ちに待った今日は 特別な日
Today is the special day I've been waiting for
いつもの日から 飛び出して
Jumping out from the usual days
ほらシャッターを切っても 写せない
Look, even if you capture it
想い出が いつでも待っている
The memories are always waiting
春も夏も秋も冬も
Spring, summer, autumn, and winter too
この場所で 見つけたい笑顔が
The smiles I want to find in this place
ひらひらと いくつも積もっていく
Are fluttering and piling up one after another
さあ次は いつ会いにいけるかな
Now, when can I go to meet you next?
当たり前から抜け出して
Breaking out from the ordinary
限界のない冒険の旅
A journey of adventure without limits
回る地球儀を目印に
With the spinning globe as our landmark
さあ会いに行こう 特別な一日に
Now let's go meet a special day
すごい、あれだけ魔法使ったのに、なんか逆に元気出てきてない？
Amazing, even after using that much magic, don't you feel even more energetic?
やっぱさ、あれじゃん？みんなから応援もらえたからじゃん！
I guess it's because... you know? We got support from everyone!
うん、みんながいるから、僕らもこうして頑張れる。
Yeah, because everyone is here, we can keep working hard like this.
いつも応援してくれてるみんなも、誰かの力になれる誰かってことなのならね。
If everyone who always supports us is also someone who can be a source of strength for others, that's great.
そうそう、シオンたちの力になってくれてる。
That's right, you're becoming Shion and the others' strength.
じゃあリスナーの皆様も魔法少女ってことで…
So that means all of you listeners are magical girls too...
ん、ね？
...Right?
みんな、いつもありがとう！
Everyone, thank you as always!
魔法少女になった僕たちのこと、これからも応援よろしくね！
Please continue to support us who have become magical girls!
みんな、魔法少女のみこたちどうだったかな？
Everyone, how were Miko and the others as magical girls?
エリートだった？
Were we elite?
これからも応援よろしくね！
Please continue to support us!
みんな、今日はありがちゅ！
Everyone, thank you for today!
ホロウィッチの魔法がみんなにも届いてたら嬉しいのなら！
I'd be happy if Holowitches' magic reached all of you!
君たちのパワーで、セクシーな魔法少女になれました。
With your power, I was able to become a sexy magical girl.
これからもたくさん応援してくださいね！
Please give us lots of support from now on too!
みんな、どうだった？楽しんでくれたかな？
Everyone, how was it? Did you enjoy it?
いつもいつも、シオンたちのこと応援してくれてありがとう。
Thank you for always, always supporting Shion and the others.
うわー緊張した！
Wow, I was so nervous!
けどみんなの応援に元気をもらって乗り切れたよ！
But I was able to get through it thanks to everyone's support!
本当にありがとうございました！
Thank you so much!
みんなから力をもらえたおかげで、もう一曲いけそうのなら！
Thanks to the strength we got from everyone, it seems like we can do one more song!
みんな、ホロウィッチの魔法、最後まで見ていってください。
Everyone, please watch Holowitches' magic until the end.
最後の曲、聴いてください。
Please listen to our last song.
せーの！
One, two...!
On your side!
キラキラ
Sparkling
宝石みたいに輝いてる
Shining like a jewel
夢の結晶
A crystal of dreams
みんなの宝物
Everyone's treasure
時々
Sometimes
見失っちゃうこともあるけれど
I might lose sight of it, but
溢れ出した
Overflowing
光が僕を呼ぶんだよ
The light is calling out to me
絶対
Definitely
大丈夫
It'll be okay
ただ
Just
まっすぐでいることも
Staying true to yourself
楽じゃない日もあるよね
There are days when it's not easy
諦めも
Giving up
苦しみも
Suffering
隠さなくていい
You don't have to hide it
心解き放とう
Let's release our hearts
夢を歌おう
Let's sing our dreams
魔法に乗せて
On the wings of magic
何度も立ち上がる
We'll stand up again and again
君と一緒に進んでいく
Going forward together with you
夢は 夢は
Our dreams, our dreams
まだ終わらない
Are not over yet
未来を取り戻そう
Let's take back the future
何度だって笑って
Smile as many times as it takes
もう一回歩きはじめよう
Let's start walking once again
ホロウィッチ on your side
Holowitch on your side
夢の先へ
To the other side of dreams
ワクワク
Excitement
するような日々も夢の結晶
Days like these are also a crystal of dreams
思い出して
Remember
魔法を唱えてみたら
If you try to chant magic
ドキドキ
Heart-pounding
するような君の物語
A story of yours that makes your heart race
もう一度胸に
Once more in your heart
キラリ光りだすんだよ
It'll start to shine brightly
頑張っていても
Even if you're working hard
うまくいかない
Things don't go well
日のほうが多く感じちゃったりするよね
You might feel like there are more days like that
その不安も
Even that anxiety
悲しみも
And sadness
抱えないで
Don't hold onto it
一人じゃない
You're not alone
希望の種を
The seeds of hope
明日に撒いたら
If you sow them for tomorrow
一番に輝く
They will shine the brightest
綺麗な花が咲くよ
Beautiful flowers will bloom
夢を歌おう
Let's sing our dreams
魔法に乗せて
On the wings of magic
何度も立ち上がる
We'll stand up again and again
君と一緒に進んでいく
Going forward together with you
夢は 夢は
Our dreams, our dreams
まだ終わらない
Are not over yet
未来を取り戻そう
Let's take back the future
Let's reclaim the future
何度だって　笑って
No matter how many times, let's smile
もう一回　歩きはじめよう
Let's start walking one more time
ホロウィッチ on your side
Holowitch on your side
夢の先へ
To the other side of our dreams
あれ？私...
Wait? I...
あ、先輩！すいません！
Ah, Senpai! I'm sorry!
こっちの作業はまだ終わってなくて...
This work isn't finished yet...
だよね。あれ多分期日延ばしても
Right. I don't think extending that deadline
後ろに影響出ないと思うから、話し通しとくね。
will affect things later, so I'll talk to them.
え？いいんですか？
Eh? Is that okay?
どうしようかと思ってたんです、本当。
I was really wondering what to do.
いいよいいよ。お互い無理せず。
It's fine, it's fine. Let's both not overdo it.
でも、全力で頑張ろう。フルキャストでね！
But let's give it our all. With a full cast!
フルキャスト？って何です？
Full cast? What's that?
頑張るぞ！っていうおまじない...かな？
A lucky charm to say... "let's do our best," maybe?
君に魔法をかけるよ
I'll cast a spell on you
We can spell on your side
始まりを告げる　鐘の音が響く
The sound of the bell signaling the beginning resonates
気付いた時がいつだって　スタートラインなんだ
The moment you notice is always the starting line
何者でもなかった　日々を変えたのは
What changed the days when I was nobody
見つけたばかりのちっぽけな　輝きの原石
was a tiny, newly found gemstone of brilliance
どうして私だけ　上手くいかないんだろう
Why am I the only one for whom things don't go well?
眩い世界の全てが　眩しく見えるけど
Everything in this bright world looks dazzling, though
ねえ君に　見つけてほしくて
Hey, I wanted you to find me
なりたい私になる　今こそ
To become the me I want to be, right now
そう叶えたい　掴みたい　夢があるから
Yes, because there's a dream I want to fulfill, to grasp
塞ぎ込んだ日の言葉も　全て踏み出すんだ
Even the words from those downcast days, I'll step out with them all
信じる力が　奇跡を起こすように
So that the power of belief may work a miracle
君に魔法をかけるよ
I'll cast a spell on you
We can spell on your side
叶えた望みと　変わらない願い
The fulfilled wishes and the unchanging desires
それぞれが等しく　流れてく世界で
In a world where each flows equally
何を求めて　歩き続けてるんだろう
What am I seeking as I keep walking?
いつもそんなことばかり　迷うけど
I'm always lost in thoughts like that, but
君がくれた　この空が
This sky you gave me
見えない翼を　くれたね
gave me invisible wings
そう照らしたい　届けたい　人がいるから
Yes, because there's someone I want to illuminate, to reach
一人取り残された日も　そう決めたんだ
Even on days when I was left all alone, I made up my mind
愛したい　応えたい　自分自身の声に
I want to love, to respond to the voice within myself
正解なんて　これでいい
Correct answers? This is fine
未体験の先へ
To the edge of the unexperienced
どんな場所でもいいよ
Any place is fine
どんな姿でもいい
Any form is okay
追いかけたいんだ　あの煌めきを
I want to chase after that sparkle
希望、光、痛み、全て
Hope, light, pain, everything
抱きしめて　持っていこう
I'll embrace them and carry them along
ほら繋げたい　広げたい　未知があるから
Look, because there's an unknown I want to connect, to expand
ここから始まる物語を　一緒にいこう
Let's go together on the story that begins from here
信じる力が　奇跡を起こすように
So that the power of belief may work a miracle
この手握って　一人じゃないから
Take this hand, because you're not alone
君に魔法をかけるよ
I'll cast a spell on you
We can spell on your side
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
魔法少女ホロウィッチ！ THE STAGE
Magical Girl holowitches! THE STAGE
＋アクリルパネル
+ Acrylic Panel
出演タレントの箔押し複製サイン入り！
Includes gold-stamped signatures of the talents!